Guide to the Ephemera collection, 1835-2002 MS2380
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera, 1835-2002; Series 2
  - Dedication of the Washington Monument, February 21st, 1885: ceremonies at base of monument: admit bearer to seat on platform., Undated; Series 2; 1 sheet; 8 x 12 cm. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 139
    Cataloger notes: Ticket no. 496 to dedication of the Washington Monument in Washington, D.C. In envelope with address label of Mrs. David L. Wells.
    Subjects: Washington Monument (Washington, D.C.)
  - United States Senate Chamber, Washington, D.C., 1949 ... for 81st Congress., Circa [1949]; Series 2; 1 sheet; 7 x 11 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 140
    Cataloger notes: Admission ticket to the U.S. Senate Chamber, signed by Robert F. Wagner.
    Subjects: United States. Congress. Senate. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79022161; United States. Congress. Senate. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00530422
  - The Washington post annual for the year 1883 with fifty illustrations on wood, chiefly by Darley ... and other celebrated American artists., Circa [1882]; Series 2; 46 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 20 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 141
    Cataloger notes: Bound in illustrated paper covers. DGW; Calendar with illustrations of U.S. and European sites.; Many advertisements at end.
  - Sir in behalf of the regents of the Smithsonian Institution, I have the honor to invite you to be present at the unveiling of the statue of Joseph Henry ... April 19, 1883 ... Spencer F. Baird., Circa [1883]; Series 2; 1 sheet; 21 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 142
    Cataloger notes: Invitation to unveiling of Joseph Henry Statue.
    Subjects: Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878 Statues. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79023046; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00032051; Smithsonian Institution. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79053968; Smithsonian Institution. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00532691; Statues. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01132151
  - Listen to WMAL AM63 Sept. 1-21, to win great grand opening gifts from the Pavilion at the Old Post Office, opening Sept. 13, 1983: the Pavilion at the Old Post Office., Circa [1983]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet (6 pages): illustrations; 22 x 28 cm folded to 22 x 10 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 143
    Subjects: Old Post Office and Clock Tower (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85094561; Pavilion at the Old Post Office (Washington, D.C.)
  - Capital life: Vol. 1, numbers 49 (September 11, 1947)., Circa [1947]; Series 2; 22 pages: illustrations, portraits; 17 x 7 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 144
    Cataloger notes: "Weekly pocket guide to food, fun and frolic in the nation's capital."; Cover title.
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel Periodicals.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Periodicals. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411641
  - Capital life: Vol. 2, numbers 10 (December 11, 1947)., Circa [1947]; Series 2; 22 pages: illustrations, portraits; 17 x 7 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 145
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel Periodicals.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505; Periodicals. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01411641
  - Historical directory of the District of Columbia., Circa [1922]; Series 2; 79 pages, [5] leaves of plates (1 folded): illustrations, map; 17 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 147
    Cataloger notes: "April 1922."; Cover title.; In blue and white paper covers.; Includes index.
    Subjects: Travel. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01155558; Washington (D.C.) Description and travel. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145349; Washington (D.C.) History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145352; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - Washington 60 years ago. The following paper ... was read at the meeting of the Oldest Inhabitants' Associations on the 7th April, 1880., Circa [1880?]; Series 2; 6 pages 24 cm (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 148
  - Correspondence with reference to the extension of Massachusetts Avenue: December, 1886., Circa [1886]; Series 2; 19 pages, [1] leaf of plates (folded): 1 folded map; 24 cm (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 149
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Bryan, W.B. Bibl. of the Dist. of Col., pages 111
    Subjects: Streets Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85128664; Massachusetts Ave. (Washington, D.C.)
  - The streets and roads of Washington by Frank L. Dyer., Circa [approximately 1900]; Series 2; pages [316]-330: illustrations, portrait; 24 cm (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 150
    Cataloger notes: Appears to be detached from an unidentified periodical.; Bound in gray paper covers. DGW; Caption title.
    Subjects: Streets Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85128664; Streets. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01134794; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - State historical markers of Virginia. Listing the inscriptions on all state markers on the principal highways of Virginia, with supplementary data., Circa [1941]; Series 2; 243, [1] pages 23 x 13 cm (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 152
    Cataloger notes: Fourth edition has title: State historical markers of Virginia. Colonial, revolutionary and nineteenth-century.; Page at end blank for "Memorandum."
    Subjects: Historical markers Virginia.; Historical markers. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00958139; Virginia Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2009126412; Virginia. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204597; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - Annual report upon survey of road from the Aqueduct Bridge to Mount Vernon, Virginia: being appendix CCC of the Annual report of the Chief of Engineers for 1890 by Peter C Hains., Circa 1890; Series 2; pages 3563-3580, [1] folded leaf of plates: color map; 23 cm (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 153
    Subjects: Roads Virginia. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85114551; Roads. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01098511; Aqueduct Bridge (Washington, D.C., and Va.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh88006115; Mount Vernon (Va.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n88160603; United States Aqueduct Bridge. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01334341; Virginia Mount Vernon. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01252957; Virginia. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204597
  - The inauguration by Richard Harding Davis., Circa [1897]; Series 2; pages [337]-356: illustrations; 25 cm (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 154
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Harper's new monthly magazine (August, 1897).; In green paper covers.
  - Inauguration scenes and incidents Joseph B. Bishop; with pictures by B. West Clinedinst, G. Wright, Irving R. Wiles., Circa [1897]; Series 2; pages 733-740: illustrations; 25 cm (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 155
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Detached from: The century (March, 1897).
    Subjects: Presidents United States Inauguration. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85106479; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155
  - Reports for the year ending April 30 ..., Undated; Series 2; volume; 23 cm. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 156
    Subjects: Oak Hill Cemetery Company.; Oak-Hill Cemetery (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n95803733; Cemeteries Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85021811
  - Overseas visitors in Washington: information and suggestions for international guests., Circa [195-?]; Series 2; 25 pages; 17 cm (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 157
    Subjects: Visitors, Foreign Washington (D.C.); Visitors, Foreign. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01167960; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - This is your Washington ..., Circa [1962]; Series 2; 64 pages (chiefly illustrations) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 158
  - The airways guide for visitors to Washington., Circa [1960]; Series 2; 112 pages: illustrations, map; 16 cm (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 159
  - Guide to Washington Issued by Passenger Departments, Baltimore and Ohio System., Circa [1913]; Series 2; 25 pages: illustrations, maps; 19 cm (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 160
    Cataloger notes: In white paper covers stamped in gold; paper onlay portrait of George Washington on cover. DGW
  - One day trips from Washington to historic shrines and points of interest in Maryland and Virginia., Circa [1933]; Series 2; 24 pages: illustrations; 23 cm (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 161
    Cataloger notes: In illustrated paper coverss..
    Subjects: Maryland Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008115826; Virginia Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2009126412; Washington Region Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117392; Maryland. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204739; Virginia. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204597; Washington (D.C.) Region. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01243124; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - Description of a visit to Washington, treating of the public, patriotic feelings which pervade the citizens--the public buildings ... with a stricture on Miss Fanny Kemble's Journal ... concluded with a general view of the present course of the administration ..., Circa [1835]; Series 2; 12 pages 24 cm. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 162
    Cataloger notes: By an ardent admirer of Jackson and Van Buren.; Caption title.; Disbound.; Signed: Lucy Kenney.
  - A historic corner in Washington by J.E. Roessle., 1891; Series 2; pages 484-488: illustrations; 29 cm (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 163
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Detached from: Frank Leslie's popular monthly (April, 1891).
  - Explanations and illustrations of the plan of the Smithsonian Institution by Prof. Henry., 1848; Series 2; pages [305]-317; 23 cm (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 164
    Cataloger notes: "Art. XXVIII."; Caption title.; Detached from: American journal of science and arts. 2nd series. Vol. 6, numbers 18 (Nov. 1848).; Bryan, W.B. Bib. of the District of Columbia, pages 172
  - The historic buildings of America by Benson J. Lossing., 1875; Series 2; pages 162-167: illustrations; 25 cm (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 165
    Cataloger notes: Detached from: Potter's American monthly. Vol. 4, No. 39 (March, 1875).
    Subjects: Christ Church, Alexandria. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79107955; Christ Church, Alexandria. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00536956
  - The President of the United States and Mrs. Washington request the pleasure of ... company to dine, on ... next, at ... o'clock ... 179 ... an answer is requested., Circa [between 1790 and 1797]; Series 2; 1 sheet; 10 x 14 cm in frame 18 x 22 cm (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 166
    Cataloger notes: Blank invitation to the President's House.
    Subjects: Washington, George, 1732-1799. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n86140996; Washington, George, 1732-1799. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00178100; White House (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85146483; White House (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00631324
  - 39th annual Capitol Hill house and garden tour: May 11 and 12, 1996., Circa [1996]; Series 2; 28 pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 167
  - Twelfth annual Kalorama house and embassy tour: Sunday, September 8, 1996, 12 noon-5 pagesm., Circa [1996]; Series 2; 24 unnumbered pages: illustrations, map; 23 cm (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 168
    Subjects: Historic buildings Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85061106; Historic buildings. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00957723; Kalorama Heights (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no2013018298; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Washington (D.C.) Kalorama Heights. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01317255
  - General information and list of paintings and sculpture., Circa [1941]; Series 2; 31 pages: illustrations; 24 cm (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 169
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; In white, gray, and black paper covers.; Seal of the National Gallery of Art at head of t.p.
    Subjects: Painting Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2010105783; Sculpture Washington (D.C.); Painting. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01050567; Sculpture. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01109483; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - National Gallery of Art, United States of America., Circa [1965]; Series 2; 29 pages: illustrations; 21 cm (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 170
    Subjects: National Gallery of Art (U.S.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79054426; National Gallery of Art (U.S.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00532733
  - Brief guide to the Smithsonian Institution: National Museum, National Gallery, Freer Gallery, National Zoological Park, Washington, D.C., Circa [1931?]; Series 2; 80 pages: illustrations, maps, portraits; 16 cm (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 171
    Cataloger notes: In blue and black illustrated paper covers.; Includes index.
  - Catalogue of an exhibition of paintings by contemporary American artists: purchased by the Council of the National Academy of Design from the Henry Ward Ranger Fund in accordance with the provision of the Ranger Bequest., 1929; Series 2; 17 pages, [9] leaves of plates: illustrations, portraits; 24 cm (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 172
    Cataloger notes: At head of title: National Gallery of Art.; Half title: Catalogue of Ranger exhibition.
    Subjects: 1800-1999 fast; Painting, American Exhibitions. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008108798; Painting, Modern 19th century Exhibitions. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008108833; Painting, Modern 20th century Exhibitions. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008108779; Painting, American. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01050648; Painting, Modern. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01050988; Exhibition catalogs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01424028
  - The march of America: an exhibition celebrating National Library Week, April 16-22, 1967: including the basic library of 100 titles, The march of America, published in facsimile by University Microfilms Library Services, Xerox Education Division., Circa [1967?]; Series 2; [32] pages: illustrations; 20 x 24 cm (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 173
    Cataloger notes: In white paper covers with colored illustration mounted on cover.
    Subjects: Discoveries in geography. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00894950; America Discovery and exploration Bibliography Exhibitions.; America History Bibliography Exhibitions.; United States Discovery and exploration Bibliography Exhibitions.; United States History Bibliography Exhibitions.; America. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01239786; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Bibliography Exhibition catalogs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423707; History. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01411628
  - Medical Museum of the Armed Forces Institute of Pathology., Circa [1960]; Series 2; 1 portfolio (33 sheets): illustrations, portraits; 22 cm. (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 174
    Cataloger notes: Table of contents -- 1. The Medical Museum -- 2. How the museum began -- 3. First visitors to the museum -- 4. Doctor Daniel Smith Lamb -- 5. Pioneers in the progress of medicine -- 6. Early contributors to medical history -- 7. Medical scientists other than physicians -- 8. Women in medicine -- 9. Human prenatal development -- 10. The human heart -- 11. Yang, yin and acupuncture -- 12. Indian medicine -- 13. Medical superstitions -- 14. Yellow fever -- 15. Conquerors of yellow fever -- 16. Significant events in the history of tuberculosis -- 17. Vaccination -- 18. Beaumont's observations on the digestive process -- 19. The story of plastic surgery -- 20. Miscroscope collection -- 21. The stethoscope -- 22. Navy hospital ship U.S.S. Haven -- 23. The assassination of President Lincoln -- 24. The assassination of President James A. Garfield -- 25. The Army doctor -- 26. The Army Nurse Corps.
    Subjects: Armed Forces Institute of Pathology (U.S.). Medical Museum. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n81133719; Armed Forces Institute of Pathology (U.S.). Medical Museum. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00562511; Medical museums Washington (D.C.); Medical museums. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01014375; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505
  - Twenty-fifth annual report of the Christ Child Society, Washington, D.C.: for the year ending March 25, 1915., Circa [1915]; Series 2; 72 pages: illustrations; 20 cm (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 175
    Subjects: Christ Child Society (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n93043564; Christ Child Society (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00686879
  - Report of first year's work and plans of a committee representing the leading religious forces in Washington: Protestant, Roman Catholic and Jewish: and designed to emphasize the importance to the State, society and the individual, of religion and church attendance, especially at the Capital where one-fifth of the population is in the Government service by Committee on Religious Life In The Nation's Capitol., 1936; Series 2; 47 pages; 22 cm (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 176
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Prefatory note addended: pages 31-47.
    Subjects: Religion and state Washington (D.C.); Religion and state. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01093863; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - Washington Temple: enter 12:30 pagesm.-2:30 pagesm., Oct. 18, 1974., Circa [1974]; Series 2; 1 card; 9 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 177
    Cataloger notes: Ticket for tour of the Washington Temple, Kensington, Md.
    Subjects: Washington Temple (Kensington, Md.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n95060045; Washington Temple (Kensington, Md.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00707858; Mormon Church Washington Metropolitan Area.; Mormon temples. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85133767; Mormon Church. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01026221; Mormon temples. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01026304; Washington (D.C.) Metropolitan Area. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01243122
  - The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints Washington Temple., Circa [197-]; Series 2; 1 folded sheet: illustrations; folded to 22 cm (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 178
    Subjects: Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints. Washington Temple.; Mormon temples. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85133767
  - National Gallery of Art: brief guide., Circa [1976]; Series 2; [i], 36 pages: illustrations (some color), color map, plans (some color, some folded); 22 cm (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 179
    Cataloger notes: "U.S. Government Printing Office: 1976 O--207-802"--Page 36.; Cover title.; Folded plans inside fold-out back cover.
    Subjects: National Gallery of Art (U.S.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79054426; National Gallery of Art (U.S.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00532733; Art museums Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh88006342; Art museums. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00815631; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01423871
  - Your Washington: pocket guide to the nation's capital by U.S. Department of the Interior, National Park Service., 1966; Series 2; 1 folded sheet ([12] pages): color illustrations; 24 x 21 cm folded to 24 x 11 cm (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 180
  - The Churchman's League of the District of Columbia., 1899; Series 2; 22 pages; 14 cm (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 181
    Subjects: Church buildings Washington (D.C.); Churchman's League (Washington, D.C.)
  - The Washington pocket guide., Circa [1953]; Series 2; 72 pages illustrations 21 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 182
  - Diamond chatterbox. May 22nd to May 28th, 1938., Circa [1938]; Series 2; 18 pages: illustrations; 21 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 183
  - Lucy Howard's journal. By Mrs. L.H. Sigourney ..., 1858; Series 2; 343 pages 19 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 184
    Cataloger notes: SPEC copy contains only p. 141-152 describing Washington, D.C.; BAL 17923
    Subjects: Diaries Fiction. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117517; Women Fiction. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2010118138; Diaries. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00892657; Women. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01176568; Fiction. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423787
  - U.S. National Museum., Circa [1879]; Series 2; 5 unnumbered pages; 23 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 185
    Cataloger notes: Caption title.; Solicitation of copies of publications and list of publications. Signed by Spencer F. Baird, Secretary Smithsonian Institution and Director, U.S. National Museum, November 1, 1879.; English and French.
  - The Diamond chatterbox of Washington, D.C. April 6, 1947., Circa [1947]; Series 2; 12 unnumbered pages: illustrations; 21 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 186
  - The Diamond chatterbox of Washington, D.C. May 5, 1957., Circa [1957]; Series 2; 14 pages: illustrations; 22 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 187
  - The "Red book" information and street guide of Washington, District of Columbia: including Chevy Chase, Bethesda, Edgemoor ... and others: new indexed maps., Circa [1932]; Series 2; 96 pages: maps; 16 cm. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 188
    Cataloger notes: Folded map attached to cover, pages3.; SPEC copy lacks the folded map.
    Subjects: Streets Washington (D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85128664; Streets Washington Metropolitan Area.; Streets. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01134794; Washington (D.C.) Guidebooks. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh2008117391; Washington (D.C.) Metropolitan Area. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01243122; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Guidebooks. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423871
  - What to see in D.C., 1960; Series 2; 58 pages: illustrations, maps; 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 189
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Includes indexes.